National Organization for Women, New York State Chapter; Records apap029
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1965-2011; 2; 22.17 cubic ft.
  - Plenary Sessions at New York State Convention, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Policy Concerning Chapter Convening Procedures - Draft, Undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Policy Naming Chapters, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Political Action Information, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Political Endorsement, 1977-1978; 1980; 1988 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Political Report, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Politicization of Women's Bodies for Political Gain, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - The Politics of Morality Impact on Women's Lives, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Pornography, Sexual Assault, and Battery (1 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Pornography, Sexual Assault, and Battery (2 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Pornography, Sexual Assault, and Battery (3 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Pornography, Sexual Assault, and Battery (4 of 4), 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Pornography, the Politics and Facts of a Confusing Issue, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Position Papers, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Positive Body Image Flyer, Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Postal Rate, 1984-1987 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Posters, Undated (Oversized 13)
  - Power of our Voices, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Power of Us, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Pregnant Woman in Jail Fighting for her Children, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Preliminary Report of the Ninth Circuit Gender Bias Task Force, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Presentation: The Need for No-Fault Divorce, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - President, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - President Agenda, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - President Expenses, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - President Expenses Reimbursement, Undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Presidents/Co-coordinators Caucus Financial Report, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Presidents, Report- Draft, Undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Presidents, Report- Notes, Undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Presidents, Speech, Undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Press Release- Assembly of the State of New York, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Press Release- Executive Chamber, Undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - The Prison System and Community Empowerment, Undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Privacy Amendment, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Pro-Choice Flyers, 1990; Undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Pro-Choice and Football Petition Notice, Undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Pro-Choice Hour, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Pro-Choice is Pro-Privacy, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Pro-Choice Pledge, Undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Pro-Choice Women Candidates Recommended for Support by Various Organization and Individuals, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Proclamation, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Professional Women in NYS, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Profit and Loss Budget vs. Actual Budget, 2010-2011 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Program on Divorce Meditation- Association of the Bar, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Programs, 1970-1981 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Progression Toward Constitutional Equality for All Us Citizens, Undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Project on the Status and Education of Women, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Project Stand Up for Women- NOW Guidelines for Activists, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Project Stop the Abortion Ban, Undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Promise Keepers, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Promise Keepers Mobilization Project, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Proportions of Women and Men who Voted for Hillary Clinton in the Super Tuesday Races, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Proposal to Hold 1991 NOW Conference in New York City Presented to the National NOW Board by NOW- NYC, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Proposal to NOW Political Development Grant- North Miami NOW, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Proposed Agendas, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Prospective Nominee Information, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Protecting Young Women's Lives, Undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Protecting Young Women's Right to Abortion: A Guide to Parental Notification and Consent Laws, Undated (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - PRYBA, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Psychological Gang Bang of Hillary is Proof We Need a Woman President, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Public Forum on Harassment, Bias-Harassment and Bullying in NY Public Schools, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Public Hearing on Women's Health, Undated (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Queens, NY Chapter, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Questions Directed to NOW- NYS Presidents, Undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Questions for Lawyers and Judges, Undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Questions for NOW- Jim Marques, Undated (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Rally Against NYS Budget Cuts, Undated (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Rally for the ERA, Undated (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Rape, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Reclaiming the "F" Word or Why Feminism Still Matters, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Records Management Service Order, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Redefining Liberation- Action Guide, Undated (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Regents- Board, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Regional Board Meeting, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Regional Conference, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Regional Conference- Philadelphia, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Regional Newsletter, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Registration Lists, Undated (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Rejoin NOW!, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Religious Belief and Public Mortality: A Catholic Governor's Perspective, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Remarks by Elizabeth Holtzman at Her Inauguration as New York City Comptroller, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Remarks by Noreen Connell- 2009 Woman to Woman Award (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - A Remembrance of Dr. Marguerite J. Fisher, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Reminders on Marcia Gillespie, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Renee Berry-Huffman, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Reorganization Meeting Agenda, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Report from the Front Lines: Impact of Violence on Poor Women, 1996; 1998 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Report from NOW/NYS Legislative Vice President, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Report of Women, Work, and Poverty, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Report on the First International Conference on Jewish Feminism, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Reports- Ohio NOW, Undated (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Reports to the National Board, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Reproduction, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Reproductive Choice: The 90's Decade of Decisions, Undated (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Reproductive Freedom Project- Annual Report, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Reproductive Rights, 1982; 1988 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Reproductive Rights Calendar, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Reproductive Rights Task Force, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Republican Assembly Members Need to Go, Undated (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Request for Candidate Endorsement, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Resignation Letters, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Resolution Calling Upon the United States Tennis Association to End Alleged Discrimination Practices Based Upon Gender, Race and Age, Undated (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Resolution on the Issue of Free Speech, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - Resolution Regarding the Civil Rights of Roisin McAliskey, Undated (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - Resolutions, 1966; 1970; 1974-1975; 1979; Undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Resolutions Passed, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Resolutions Proposed Order of Consideration, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions Referred to the National Board, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Resource Inventory, Undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Response to No-Fault Divorce Proposal, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Resumes, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Return of Organization Exempt from Income Tax, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Revised Filing of Grievance Against Kathryn Mazierski and Christen Archer, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Rhode Island NOW, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Right to Choose PAC, 1990; Undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Rita Haley- Delegate, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Robert Bork (1 of 3), 1971; 1978; 1985; 1987 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Robert Bork (2 of 3), 1971; 1978; 1985; 1987 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Robert Bork (3 of 3), 1971; 1978; 1985; 1987 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Robert Livingston: A Profile, Undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Rockland County Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Rockland County Chapter, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Rockland County Meetings, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Roe v. Wade- 20th Anniversary Public Celebration, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Roe v. Wade- 26th Anniversary Public Celebration, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Rosina Paul- Haitian Refugee, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Round Table- Divorce, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Rules of the Office of Court Administration, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Rust v. Sullivan, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - The Ruth Community, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Safe House, 1988-1999 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Saint Patrick's- Stag Dinner, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Saint Paul Winter Carnival Protests, 1991; Undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Saratoga Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Save the Date!, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Schenectady, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Senator Bob Parkwood, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Senator Gillibrand- Childcare, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Senator Hiram Monserrate, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Senator Hiram Monserrate- Misdemeanor, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Senator Suzi Oppenheimer- Public Hearing, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Services for Separating and Divorced Women, Undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Sex Crimes: Ten Years on the Front Lines, Prosecuting Rapists and Confronting their Collaborators, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Sex Discrimination, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Sex Discrimination in Education, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - The Sex Panic: Women, Censorship and "Pornography", Undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Sexism in the American Workplace, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Sexual Harassment- Marcia Pappas Speech, Undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Shaping Women's Political Future in the 21st Century, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Sharon L. Fawley- Public Information Vice President, Undated (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Sheila Molnar, 1973-1975; 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Shirley U. Graber Scholarship Fund, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - The Shoulders We Stand on 40 Years of Activism, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Silent Auction, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Single Working Mothers Letters to- Antonie K. Hoffman, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Sisterhood of Black Single Mothers, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - The Six Battered Mothers Custody Conference, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Small Justice - Little Justice in America's Family Courts - A Video By Garland Waller, Undated (Vhs 1)
  - Smith- Barney Settlement, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Social Security, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Societal Perception of Women, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - South Shore, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - South Suffolk Chapter, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - South Suffolk Chapter- Annual Holiday Program, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - South Suffolk NOW- General Meeting, Undated (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Southern Westchester Chapter, 1979-1982 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Speak-Out- Save Women's Lives, Undated (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Speakers, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Speakers Bureau, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Speech, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Speech on Employment Discrimination, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Speech on Reproductive Rights, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Spring Celebration/ Bread and Roses Award Ceremony, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Staff, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - State Board Meeting Tips, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - State Conference- Ossining, NY, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - State Conference Packet, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - State Convention, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - State Coordinators, 1986; 1989-1993; 2000; Undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - State Coordinators' Caucus, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - State Coordinators' Caucus History and Operation Guide Book, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - State Coordinators' Conference, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - State Council, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - State Council Affirmative Action Survey and Report- Putting our Commitment to the Test or Affecting Change from Within, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - State Council Delegates, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - State Council Meetings, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - State Level- Roe v. Wade- Agenda for State NOW, Undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - The State of Black America, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - State Regional Meetings, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Statement from Francoise Jacobsohn- Gina Feliciano, Undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Statement on New Activist and Leadership Training Institute, Undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Statements on Mandatory Meditation of Child Custody and Child Support Disputes, 1985; 1994-1996; Undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Statements on Supreme Court's Decision on Minor Rights, Undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Staten Island Chapter, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Status on Legislative Efforts to Overturn the Gag Rule, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Status Report- Pay Equality Project, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Step by Step Organization Plan, Undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Stockholder's Action, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Stop the Terrorism- Understanding Your Rights Under the Freedom of Access to Clinic Entrances Act, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - STOP Violence Against Women, Undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Study on How NOW Chapters Survive- Ohio State, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Sue Larsen- Complaint, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Suffolk County NOW, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Suffolk Court House, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Summary Report - Leadership Skills Training Program, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Summit on Economic Justice for Woman, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Supplement to Protective Parent Reform Act, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Support for ERA-Letter to Bill Clinton, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Support for Women's Lives Form, Undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Supreme Court Briefing- Sexual Harassment Cases Before the Court, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Supreme Court Nomination Action Resolution, Undated (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Supreme Court Press Briefing, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - "Surrogate" Parenting, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Survey- Mothers on Trial, Undated (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Survey of NOW Chapter Activity, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Tag Day- Fundraising, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Talia Carner, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Talking Back: Getting Your Message Out, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Tammy Bruce, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Task Force Chain, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Task Force Expense Vouchers, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Task Force- Heads, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Task Forces (1 of 2), 1971-1976; 1980-1982; 1985 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Task Forces (2 of 2), 1971-1976; 1980-1982; 1985 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Task Forces and Chapter Delegate Lists, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Tawana Brawley, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Tax Exempt Financial Report, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Tax Proposals, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Team Building, Undated (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Team NOW- Contact Sheets, Undated (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Team NOW- Gloria Woods, Undated (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Team NOW- Marcia Pappas, Undated (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Team NOW- NYS Endorsements, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Team NOW- Toni Van Pelt, Undated (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Teen Pregnancy, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Tennessee NOW, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Testimony- Matrimonial Actions, 1993; 1996 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Testimony of Francoise Jacobsohn, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Testimony of Melodie Bahan- President of NOW NYC to NYC Council on State and Federal Legislation, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Testimony of Molly Yard- U.S. House of Representatives Committee on Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Testimony of NOW by Patricia Ireland Before a Committee of the National Associations of Security Dealers (NASD), 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Testimony of NOW- Violence Against Women Act II- Draft, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Testimony on the Tolling of the Statute of Limitations in the Case of Sexual Abuse, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Thank You- Janice Burns, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Thank You's- Legislatures, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Thinking About Tactics for Political and Social Change, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Tompkins County NOW- Guide to the 1988 Presidential Election, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1992; 1996-1998; 2005 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Treasury- Laura Rosman, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Troy, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - The Truth About George Campaign Sample Op-Ed Draft, 2002; Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Turning the Tide for Equality, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Ulster County Conference Site, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Ulster NOW Chapter, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Ulster NOW- Zip Codes, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - UN Conference on Discrimination and Development, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Unbought and Unbossed, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Unbought and Unbossed: Some Leaders are Born Women, Undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - United States Elections, 1988-1992 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - United States Senate Members, Undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - University at Albany- School of Social Welfare Interns, 1986-1988; Undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - University NOW, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Unsung Heroine Awards, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Updated Volunteer List, Undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Upstate Editorial Page Editors, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Utah NOW, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Utica Chapter, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - UUSCR Women's Group Presents Thank Goodness it's Friday, 2007; Undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Violence Against Women Prevention, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Virginia NOW, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Vision Committee, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Vision NOW- Facilitator Notes, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Vision of Women Awards, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Visioning NOW- Facilitator Notes, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - "A Visit From Alice Paul"- Barbra Celona, Undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Vital Importance of Nonviolence Training Sessions, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Voices for Choice- Mid-Suffolk Chapter Annual Dinner, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Voting Guide, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Walk- Assemblymen, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Walmart- Merchant of Shame/ Op-Ed, 2002; Undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - We Feminist United, Undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - We the Women, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Web Redesign Presentation to National Board, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Weinstein v. Korn Miller, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Welfare, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Well Women Project, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - West Virginia NOW, Undated (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - What Did They Expect, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - "What NOW" Forum, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Where Women made History, Undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - White House Interdepartmental Task Force on Women, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Why is NOW-NYS Opposing a Law that Benefits Women, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Who Cares About Women's Rights- N.O.W. Cares, Undated (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - William K. Rashbaum, MD- In his Own Words, Undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Winter of My Discontent- Valerie Sullivan, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Wizard of ID, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Women After Divorce: Preliminary Report from a 10-Year Follow-Up, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Women and Healthcare: Examining Inequities, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Women Helping Women- Awards Dinner, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Women and HIV Infection Conference, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Women and Men Working Together for Equality, Undated (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Women and Unpaid Work: A Feminist Strategy, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Women in the Courts, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Women in the Courts II, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Women in Government- Cuomo Appointments, 1986; Undated (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Women in Office: Winning our Rights- Regional Conference, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Women in Politics: Advancing a Feminist Agenda- Panel, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Women Making History, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Women of Color and Allies Summit: Linking Arms in Dangerous Times, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Women of Color and Allies Summit Planning Meeting, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Women of NYS Legislature, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Women Photograph Women, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Women, Power, and Spirituality Annual Dinners, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Women with Opinions: Rise Up and Be Heard, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Women's Activism Brochures, Undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Women's Appointments Alliance, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Women's Conference, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Women's Connection- Spring, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Women's Employment Forum, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Women's Equality Awards, 1989; 1991 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Women's Equality Day, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Women's Equality, Women's Lives, 1989; 1992 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Women's Health Project, Undated (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Women's History Month Essay Contest, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Women's Labor Day Rally, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Women's Landmark Preservation Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Women's Night Out- 14th Annual Conference, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Women's Resource Guide to NYC, Undated (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Women's Rights Convention- Declaration of Sentiments, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Women's Rights in NYS, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - "Women's Rights Without Feminism A Dead End for Women", Undated (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Women's Unit- Executive Chamber, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Wood Postcard, Undated (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Woodbury Karate School, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Working Conference on Women and Social Security, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Workmen's Compensation Set Aside- Ruth Jardines, 1978-1979; 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - Workshop Information, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - Workshops and Hearing Issues, Undated (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - World Demands of the March, Undated (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - World March of Women in 2000 (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Write-In for Women's Rights, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 104)
  - The Wrongs of the So-Called "Right", Undated (Box 21, Folder 105)
  - Young Feminist Summit, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Young Feminist Summit on Violence, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Young Feminist Task Force Essay Winner- Jennifer Erland, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Young Women of Achievement Awards Ceremony, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Zelle Andrews, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Zip Codes in NY Counties, Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Issues Files, 1961-2011; 3; 8.4 cubic ft.